Step 1: click (414, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I need to search for 'ChatGPT' to see its trend. Looking at the page, I can se
Step 2: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. There is a search bar at the top of the trending topics list with placeholder
Step 3: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. Looking at the screenshot, there is a search bar near the top of the page with
Step 4: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. Looking at the screenshot, I notice there is a search bar near the top of the
Step 5: find_and_click (672, 349) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search bar at the top of the trending topics list with pla
Step 6: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. There is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' near the t
Step 7: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. There is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' near the t
Step 8: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' n
Step 9: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' n
Step 10: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' n
Step 11: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' n
Step 12: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. There is a search input field with placeholder text 'Search trends' near the t
Step 13: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field near the top of the page with placehold
Step 14: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open. I notice there is a search input field near the top of the page with placehold
Step 15: click (591, 336) [OK]\NI can see the Google Trends page is open with a search input field visible at the top of the trending list. The search b